<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ecosystem on OpenAerialMap Docs</title>
    <link>/ecosystem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ecosystem on OpenAerialMap Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/ecosystem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/ecosystem/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ecosystem/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>OpenAerialMap Ecosystem Imagery from satellites, unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs) and other aircraft is becoming increasingly available after a disaster. It is often difficult to determine what is available and easily access it. OpenAerialMap (OAM) seeks to solve this by providing a simple open way to host and provide access to imagery for humanitarian response and disaster preparedness.
OpenAerialMap relies on a set of open source tools to accomplish its goals. These components can be divided into two main functionalities:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalog Group</title>
      <link>/ecosystem/catalog-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ecosystem/catalog-group/</guid>
      <description>Catalog Components Components that index and serve imagery metadata. The Open Imagery Network (OIN) specification allows providers to annotate their imagery with metadata and register them to the network in a standard way. The OAM Catalog is a collection of OIN spec&amp;rsquo;d metadata.
OAM API The OAM API in the main component of this group. It contains two sub-components that work together to provide imagery metadata to users: The worker and the catalog API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors Group</title>
      <link>/ecosystem/contributors-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ecosystem/contributors-group/</guid>
      <description>Contributor Components Components that allow a contributor to add data to the system through an upload form. The data is added to the HOTOSM imagery bucket. Contributors with a large amount of imagery should consider setting up their own imagery bucket within the OIN network.
OAM Uploader A web form that a contributor can use to add datasets to OpenAerialMap. This form requires an access token for authorization, which can be requested from an OpenAerialMap team member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll Your Own</title>
      <link>/ecosystem/roll-your-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ecosystem/roll-your-own/</guid>
      <description>For development purposes, you can roll parts of OpenAerialMap locally. Detailed docs exist in the README section of each component. This document is an overview of the interdependencies and configuring the development environment as a functional whole.
Development Requirements   It will be necessary to use nvm during development - some applications will need Node v4, others will use Node v0.12
  In some components (the web frontends) configuration variables can be added to app/assets/scripts/config/local.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
