<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uploader on OpenAerialMap Docs</title>
    <link>/uploader/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uploader on OpenAerialMap Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/uploader/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/uploader/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uploader/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>OpenAerialMap Uploader The OAM imagery database is made up of the contributions of users.
Learn more about how to upload.
The OAM uploader consists of two different tools:
 the upload form and the server to glue everything together  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Api Server</title>
      <link>/uploader/api-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uploader/api-server/</guid>
      <description>The API server handles everything related to imagery upload: actual uploads and processing.
Upload To be developed. Good things come to those who wait&amp;hellip;
Processing To be developed. Good things come to those who wait&amp;hellip;
Further documentation Check out the full API documentation for information on the imagery upload related endpoints.
Source code and development The oam-uploader-api is completely open source and the code and instructions are available on github under the BSD 3-Clause license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uploader Form</title>
      <link>/uploader/uploader-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uploader/uploader-form/</guid>
      <description>The upload form is the way for users to contribute to the OAM imagery database. Besides uploading the imagery itself, contributors need to provide metadata for imagery datasets. There are two types of fields for filling in the metadata: fields for input values (Title, Sensor, Provider, Tags, Contact info) and fields with choices (Platform, Date start, Date end, Contact, License).
Also, there is an opportunity to upload several imagery datasets by clicking on the &amp;ldquo;New dataset&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
