<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uploader on OpenAerialMap Docs</title>
    <link>/uploader/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uploader on OpenAerialMap Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/uploader/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/uploader/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uploader/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>OpenAerialMap Uploader The OAM imagery database is made of the contributions of users, but to ensure the quality and accuracy of the contents the uploaders need to be approved.
Users have to request a token which then can be used in the upload form to validate their identity. Learn more about how to upload.
The OAM uploader consists of three different tools:
 the upload form the token manager app and the server to glue everything together  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Api Server</title>
      <link>/uploader/api-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uploader/api-server/</guid>
      <description>The API server handles everything related to imagery upload, from user tokens to the actual uploads and processing.
Upload To be developed. Good things come to those who wait&amp;hellip;
Processing To be developed. Good things come to those who wait&amp;hellip;
Further documentation Check out the full API documentation for information on the imagery upload related endpoints.
Source code and development The oam-uploader-api is completely open source and the code and instructions are available on github under the BSD 3-Clause license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Token Manager</title>
      <link>/uploader/token-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uploader/token-manager/</guid>
      <description>The token is a hexadecimal access code that allows the upload of imagery to the OAM database. Administrators can create and manage tokens using the admin interface.
Since tokens are not tied to a specific user, a description allows the admin to keep track of the purpose of each one.
Tokens can have an expiracy date, a feature that is useful if the token is being generated, for example, for a mapping event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uploader Form</title>
      <link>/uploader/uploader-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uploader/uploader-form/</guid>
      <description>The upload form is the way for users to contribute to the OAM imagery database.
Token Users need a valid token to submit imagery. This helps the OAM team ensure the quality of the submitted materials.
The token can be requested either by email or through a github issue. When done via the &amp;ldquo;Request token&amp;rdquo; button on the upload form the email/issue will have a template prompting the user for all the needed information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
